
   const questions = [
      {
        "question": "Who is the main protagonist of Hunter X Hunter?",
        "options": ["Gon Freecss", "Killua Zoldyck", "Kurapika", "Leorio Paradinight"],
        "answer": "Gon Freecss"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the magic power system in Black Clover called?",
        "options": ["Nen", "Ki", "Magic", "Chakra"],
        "answer": "Magic"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which demon is the main antagonist in Demon Slayer?",
        "options": ["Rui", "Muzan Kibutsuji", "Akaza", "Enmu"],
        "answer": "Muzan Kibutsuji"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is Naruto's signature move?",
        "options": ["Chidori", "Rasengan", "Shadow Clone", "Sage Mode"],
        "answer": "Rasengan"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the name of Eren Yeager’s titan in Attack on Titan?",
        "options": ["Attack Titan", "Founding Titan", "Armored Titan", "Beast Titan"],
        "answer": "Attack Titan"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which member of the Phantom Troupe is known as the 'Big Brother'?",
        "options": ["Chrollo Lucilfer", "Feitan", "Hisoka", "Kurapika"],
        "answer": "Feitan"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Black Clover character is a royal with the power of light magic?",
        "options": ["Yuno", "Asta", "Noelle Silva", "Fuego Leon"],
        "answer": "Yuno"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who is the water Hashira in Demon Slayer?",
        "options": ["Giyu Tomioka", "Kanao Tsuyuri", "Shinobu Kocho", "Mitsuri Kanroji"],
        "answer": "Giyu Tomioka"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who becomes the 7th Hokage in Naruto?",
        "options": ["Sasuke Uchiha", "Naruto Uzumaki", "Kakashi Hatake", "Minato Namikaze"],
        "answer": "Naruto Uzumaki"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the name of the wall surrounding humanity in Attack on Titan?",
        "options": ["Wall Maria", "Wall Rose", "Wall Sina", "Wall Sheena"],
        "answer": "Wall Maria"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is Killua's most powerful ability in Hunter X Hunter?",
        "options": ["Godspeed", "Hunter's Eye", "Zetsu", "Scarlet Eyes"],
        "answer": "Godspeed"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is Asta's biggest disadvantage in Black Clover?",
        "options": ["No magic", "Weak physical strength", "No sword", "No friends"],
        "answer": "No magic"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who is the Demon Slayer's main antagonist?",
        "options": ["Kanao Tsuyuri", "Muzan Kibutsuji", "Rengoku Kyojuro", "Zenitsu Agatsuma"],
        "answer": "Muzan Kibutsuji"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the village that Naruto is from?",
        "options": ["Hidden Leaf Village", "Hidden Mist Village", "Hidden Sand Village", "Hidden Cloud Village"],
        "answer": "Hidden Leaf Village"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the name of Eren's father in Attack on Titan?",
        "options": ["Grisha Yeager", "Zeke Yeager", "Rico Yeager", "Aaron Yeager"],
        "answer": "Grisha Yeager"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is Gon’s main goal in Hunter X Hunter?",
        "options": ["To become the strongest Hunter", "To find his father", "To make money", "To defeat Hisoka"],
        "answer": "To find his father"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is Noelle Silva's magic type in Black Clover?",
        "options": ["Water Magic", "Fire Magic", "Wind Magic", "Earth Magic"],
        "answer": "Water Magic"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which demon slayer uses the Thunder Breathing technique?",
        "options": ["Inosuke Hashibira", "Zenitsu Agatsuma", "Tanjiro Kamado", "Kanao Tsuyuri"],
        "answer": "Zenitsu Agatsuma"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who is the leader of the Akatsuki in Naruto?",
        "options": ["Itachi Uchiha", "Nagato/Pain", "Kisame Hoshigaki", "Madara Uchiha"],
        "answer": "Nagato/Pain"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Titan is able to control other Titans in Attack on Titan?",
        "options": ["Attack Titan", "Colossal Titan", "Founding Titan", "Armored Titan"],
        "answer": "Founding Titan"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which is the first arc of Hunter X Hunter?",
        "options": ["Greed Island", "Yorknew City", "Zoldyck Family", "Hunter Exam"],
        "answer": "Hunter Exam"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who is the Black Bull's captain in Black Clover?",
        "options": ["Yami Sukehiro", "Asta", "Noelle Silva", "Mimosa Vermillion"],
        "answer": "Yami Sukehiro"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is Zenitsu's main fear in Demon Slayer?",
        "options": ["Demons", "Darkness", "Thunder", "Women"],
        "answer": "Demons"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Naruto character is known for the Rasengan?",
        "options": ["Minato Namikaze", "Kakashi Hatake", "Naruto Uzumaki", "Jiraiya"],
        "answer": "Naruto Uzumaki"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the original Titan Shifter in Attack on Titan?",
        "options": ["Eren Yeager", "Grisha Yeager", "Ymir Fritz", "Zeke Yeager"],
        "answer": "Ymir Fritz"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the name of Kurapika's Nen ability in Hunter X Hunter?",
        "options": ["Chain Jail", "Ren", "Bungee Gum", "Mantra"],
        "answer": "Chain Jail"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which of the following is Asta’s sword in Black Clover?",
        "options": ["Demon-Slayer Sword", "Spirit Sword", "Anti-Magic Sword", "Magic Sword"],
        "answer": "Anti-Magic Sword"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who is Tanjiro's sister in Demon Slayer?",
        "options": ["Mitsuri", "Nezuko Kamado", "Kanao Tsuyuri", "Shinobu Kocho"],
        "answer": "Nezuko Kamado"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Naruto character becomes the Tailed Beast Jinchuriki?",
        "options": ["Naruto Uzumaki", "Sasuke Uchiha", "Gaara", "Killer Bee"],
        "answer": "Naruto Uzumaki"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which attack is used by Eren Yeager in Attack on Titan?",
        "options": ["Titan Roar", "Titan Shifter", "Attack Titan", "Final Smash"],
        "answer": "Titan Roar"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who is the strongest member of the Zoldyck family in Hunter X Hunter?",
        "options": ["Silva Zoldyck", "Zeno Zoldyck", "Killua Zoldyck", "Illumi Zoldyck"],
        "answer": "Zeno Zoldyck"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the main focus of the Clover Kingdom in Black Clover?",
        "options": ["To defeat the dark triad", "To control magic", "To create a magic empire", "To find a magic stone"],
        "answer": "To defeat the dark triad"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who is the Demon Slayer who uses Water Breathing?",
        "options": ["Kanao Tsuyuri", "Tanjiro Kamado", "Giyu Tomioka", "Shinobu Kocho"],
        "answer": "Giyu Tomioka"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which of the following Naruto characters possesses the Sharingan?",
        "options": ["Sasuke Uchiha", "Naruto Uzumaki", "Sakura Haruno", "Kakashi Hatake"],
        "answer": "Sasuke Uchiha"
      }
    ]
